oh yeah and then you know start the car
oh yeah we have a button at the car we
can't we can't ask too much afford it
definitely just started unlocked it now
start did it oh wait you know there was
like a little guide that came with the
other key I don't know there's too hard
yeah yeah it's too high just hurtin this
car is seriously so sweet you guys first
of all look at these blue lights they're
so swanky and then when George starts
the car they turned red did you notice
those George
yeah oh it's so take the sticker off oh
no it's gonna be hard
why would they do this sticker is gonna
leave sticker resident it's a really
sticker yeah automobiles the components
replacement parts and maintenance
they're off contained chemicals don't
wanna bro no fuck California man making
me like deal with this shit now that's
on my car sweet let's go
wow this is a lot of things oh that's
that's kind of bright yeah that was good
alright maybe not all the bad things I
said about forward we have a few
criticisms but this is my new car
oh yeah the cupholders that light up
alright go there's a civic over there it
looks so quaint yes
oh it's nice this car is actually real
nice um I mean look okay their logo like
their logo needs help but apart from
that apart from that so okay we
downloaded their first app like the my
Ford Connect app and it was rated 2.5
stars I'm more like okay that's what we
expect from a car company the other new
apps apparently rated 4.5 Wow so that's
pretty good I don't even think Ford paid
those reviewers it was Duke so I would
say they paid a button some people but
not for it anymore cuz hate for Ford's
over hateful Ford is over not only is
hate for Ford over but if 2016 was the
year of the Honda and 2017 was the year
of the Toyota 2018 is the year the for
its 40 year that's right there's no
that's Vivian's last name that's true
that's you that means it's my year
that's right all right let's get on the
road okay so this car does not drive
itself which is a everybody for that
notice take this outside
I'm not self-driving car let's see other
downsides of a not self-driving car wait
wait
so let's engage the for its self-driving
features so let's engage into active
cruise control okay okay it's also got a
lane keep assist alleged
but it doesn't see the lanes they show
up green when it sees the lanes we're
gonna hack this with some open pilot
goodness real soon getting good at
hacking the cars bro but okay so this
car does have adaptive cruise control
and Link you persist and self-park yeah
now the adaptive cruise control the lane
keep assist with southpark all come in
completely different packages so you
have to buy three upgrade packages to
get all of them or you can just go ball
out and buy the Platinum package which
includes them all affording complain is
it that's right it's nine is it nine
it's ten what that was a terrible
experience doesn't have a GPS f-150 Broz
yeah maybe yo you guys know when it was
the Toyotas do we buy your the four and
how many Ford's are we gonna buy but our
gear let's see if we get the link
certainly keep it all and so allegedly
this cruise control works and stop and
go
trying struggling I'm struggling here
how to use it let's sweet breath into
two two this is wide open pilot has one
button phone oh that's a tragedy
I'm sorry Skokie's well we'll be around
your little power mode will last it will
kinda last yeah but ok so notice how I'm
like way over the lane line over there
I'm in adaptor cancels yeah how it
cancels out to 3 seconds okay oh wait it
automatically resumed okay that was
scary and um yep you cancels it should
not if you cancel this should not
automatically resume that bad design
okay so this car doesn't have like the
lane keep allegedly supposed to do
something by the way we heard that forth
you want to show up the thing that's
supposed to be sure was lovely she was
so much more lovely she's watching she
was so much more lovely than the people
at home the the last guys at Honda don't
deal with them you go home I wasn't
going home during fourthly we had good
conversation Kristin you girl alright
we're gonna go to the highway no we're
gonna go home because you guys have
already seen everything in the Ford the
list all there is to it might seem that
doesn't work they didn't try adaptive
cruise control on we did we did we did
but with the break we did it did break
no it did three well kind of and then it
canceled oh that was the car doing yeah
yeah you didn't mention it
so let's make u-turn here oh my god this
is so hard alright
no those radius the turn radius is
pretty nice and for the last thing when
we get back to the house we will show
them will storm so far yeah see if we'll
see if the south part is going to work
the year of the Ford no what about the
what's about the year of the fort this
is a great year guys you were two blimps
this is a great year yeah that's right
mark fields is that his name or did that
guy get fired okay so the lane keep is
on now so it's gonna lane keep allegedly
keep hands on steering wheel okay I
understand
okay no it cancels one two one two okay
so it stays on for about three seconds
so my press resume I'm that time outs
not in the PCM open pilot just might not
have that restrictions like super cruise
I think but guys if you guys saw like
the difference between me driving here
with open highlights yeah but let's see
if we can get it to park all the Ford
the Ford logo really does need help yeah
it just still looks so it just looks
like when did I buy this car like Ford
and coca-cola are really stuck on their
old logos okay coca-cola fine no
coca-cola looks very similar it's the
same type of it's different chemical is
a softer you want a classic soft drink
you don't want new technology you're
softer but I want a classic car you know
good Ford Tough that feels very cool a
fine fine maybe it's an appropriate bad
for the pickup trucks but here they are
trying to put in all this technology
right like it just doesn't look right
except by that yeah porn if you're out
listening if they said I had any
problems at all gonna bring it back I'll
return it no return it bring it back
classic car I'm with cancel cancel
cancel the year the Ford go will buy to
suit
you're gonna drive a Subaru next year's
good sorry Subarus don't get your hopes
up but this is the Earl afford 2018 is
the year the Ford my Ford GT instead
uh-oh
high 42 yeah I'm not that rich guys this
is the other Ford I don't know what you
it's gonna be next year but this is the
other part okay let's try this that
button now notice how it looks like it
was made in like god I don't even know I
mean kind of oh I have options here
about that okay perpendicular parallel
okay I stopped the vehicle I really I'm
worrying about this cuz like there's
just three cars
[Music]
oh we're gonna crash the house okay okay
this looks okay the UI looks horrendous
it's except for the fact that we're
parking right in this person's driveway
oh and that seems like it's tight it's
good it knows what it's doing
but how - is that moving steering way
all right back up prepare to stop
finished okay have you done honestly to
check the car yeah well I wanted to see
it for we did really well
oh good job Ford but I think we're in
their driveway in the driveway through
backup well they warned you know before
so we definitely they've given you a
note yes that is some passive aggressive
as sorry neighbors we love you fire
classic fire alright and that is a Ford
Fusion Hybrid energy it has this
terrible sticker on the window which I'm
deeply upset about it has practically
not why do I like this car I honestly I
got sold because it looks really also
got ripped off at the four - also not
really ripped off the grass they did
they did pull a little trick it has like
all of this nice stuff that you want you
know this car has tiny buttons never
mind I hate this car let's go back they
wanna buy a Ford Fusion will give you uh
let's see how's the stereo
[Music]
here with the Sony oh did someone say
you can't have this it's a Sony I didn't
see it I didn't I didn't see it I don't
think it's anxious somebody I think Sony
just like this is a brand name Dupree
shit yeah how many showbiz you got 50
sick yo check out the movie if you can't
see a thing all right well that is that
is our Ford Fusion the tape over it we
will so do you Matt part two George here
we go no no no we're friends with Sony
now we're friends with Sony you guys are
friends I don't know why I like this car
I'm looking at it now okay all right
this leather this Coco leather is really
nice do you like the cold air it's well
it's a you want to take less cold oh
okay no stop being dual you're messing
it up wait it's 61 degrees outside why
is it blowing 70 degree freezing it AC
it's not that doesn't even wait Oh click
on that there we go oh I see if machs AC
does that but can I have max
this is so cold we want you don't want
the coin this is so confusing okay so
you're getting to show this to them you
can do max AC which is that you can turn
that off and shut that off but then I
can turn that on and then what's that is
that max it's AC coming from I
understand yeah but notice that you
can't have max AC without that okay I
turn that on I turn that off it turns
off oh wait why did it go too low oh I
think cuz I've been on Max's let's check
out let's do a review of their nav
system oh my god oh my god oh my god
what they'll know where we live Oh
oh my god I would like honestly if I got
an iPhone and it was like that I'd be
like screaming the Apple Store that's
way more like good oh and now it's going
a hot air that's so hot so you put it's
okay never mind never gonna solve
self-driving cars the shit is unusable
[Laughter]
audio sirius satellite radio because
they know the sticker on the windshield
nice what apps do we have yeah
oh we can oh that's cool oh you got a
sink you're here for ya power flow oh oh
it's going from battery to other how
much on a charge do you get this is
total crap even the Toyota ones better
okay nevermind I okay what do I like
about this car let's be positive
interior is on point interior for has
come a long way on it on their interior
this is really nice it feels really
Pleasant this honestly is nice for the
Model S I would not go that far I was in
ok again maybe it was an older model X
but I was in a Model X if I was upset
with the interior a lot yeah the
interior of this is very nice yeah they
did a really really good job it feels
really nice the leather feels super nice
this Coco leather accenting the white
leather nicer than the Civic for sure oh
this is nice oh ok
interior is good yeah all the
technologies they have all the
technology at least at least they
haven't have it I mean that's not saying
much
pretty good South Park was ok ok I like
that I like that it turns the steering
yeah I know they have no way of knowing
it's a driveway but they could know that
you have to put a camera on it
but yeah I think those are the two
things we like about this car I think
yeah obviously the interior kind of sold
me know it does have nice ride quality
yeah it actually does um you know it has
terrible ride quality
the Acura ILX yeah I think that like the
Civic has really nice ride quality I
would say this is like riding car we
have to yeah also we can't say this cars
1550s sorry
$35,000 yeah the Raveis 33 it was like
33 yeah Wow dissimilar okay this is way
nice for me Acura the Acura sweet 15
though I know it's been 2 years no no
the interior and ride quality of this
car is like the most luxurious totally
it's so pleasant and it feels like
there's so much space like I can't
really explain the space but it feels
spacious it does it just feel spacious
you know weird thing over there their
technology is I mean I can't compliment
any of the manufacturers on this yeah I
can't I can't say any of them like okay
which ones better to be honest like
that's only like a little wacky yeah
Toyota what is completely the specific
is the worst because the volume control
the volume control knob yeah this is
like when you're comparing it to some of
these other person so whatever do you
know some employees who are wrecked cars
and put shit everywhere I can't come in
the night with you guys that's pretty
much there's gonna be the next car
supported by open pilot if you're a Ford
person buy one okay I don't buy it until
the end report done but yeah it's not a
bad car it started that car I'm one of
the things we're excited about is how
much that wheel can turn
yeah we hacked up the past of the Prius
as well
so we got we got some real goods a real
target the wheels now gonna be carefully
carefully put talked to the wheels and
then we're also gonna get a hack all the
for DC use now till we got all the hacks
to the Honda's ECU's we got all the
hacks authorities use don't have parties
yes just have them all we got everybody
out of town that's gonna be an exciting
day cool
let's go fees that's been my review of
the Ford Fusion 2018 titanium Edition
2018 year of the Ford jenefor thank you
for by Scopus